{
  "title": "English grammar and vocabulary questions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "I had to keep my daughter home from school today because she had a ........ of 38 degrees. ",
      "answers": ["fever", "headache", "temperature", "warmth"],
      "correct": "temperature"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "When we were in Bali last year, we ........ at a marvelous hotel overlooking the beach. ",
      "answers": ["stopped", "lived", "rented", "stayed"],
      "correct": "stayed"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "I usually ........ up six at 6.30 a.m. every morning. ",
      "answers": ["awake", "get", "rise", "go"],
      "correct": "get"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Good afternoon. I ........ see the manager, please.",
      "answers": ["will", "wish", "like to", "want to"],
      "correct": "want to"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "I thought Nancy said she ........ spend the weekend with her parents. ",
      "answers": ["should", "will", "is", "was going to"],
      "correct": "was going to"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "I was wondering if you can ........ me to play the violin? ",
      "answers": ["assist", "teach", "learn", "study"],
      "correct": "teach"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Would you ........ this letter to the Post Office, please? ",
      "answers": ["send", "take", "retrieve", "fetch"],
      "correct": "take"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "I hate doing the ............. especially cleaning the windows. ",
      "answers": ["homework", "housework", "jobs", "groundwork"],
      "correct": "housework"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "I got married ........ years ago. ",
      "answers": ["for two", "in two", "at two", "two"],
      "correct": "two"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "I'm sorry but I haven't ........ today. ",
      "answers": [
        "read my lesson",
        "done my lesson",
        "done my homework",
        "studied my homework"
      ],
      "correct": "done my homework"
    }
  ]
}
